http://www.status.co.uk/privacy-policy/

HomePrivacy Policy
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors, clients and prospects; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.
(1) What information do we collect?
We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:
a) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services
b) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us including
Name
Organization
Address
E mail address
Telephone number
(2) Cookies
(i) A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.
We use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit.
Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.
(ii) We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.]
(iii) Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.
(3) Using your personal data
Personal data submitted on this website or to us by phone or email will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.
We may use your personal information to:
a)  Send quotations to you
b)  Send you products you have ordered
b)  send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you
c)  send you email for general correspondence and communications
d) send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications by using the opt out feature in email or in writing by e mail).
We will not provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.
(4) Disclosures
We may disclose information about you to any of our employees or official distributors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.
In addition, we may disclose information about you:
(a)  to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
(b)  in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
(c)  in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the
purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk)
(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are contemplating selling.
Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.
(5) Security of your personal data
We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers.
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.
You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. We will not ask you for your password.
(6) Policy amendments
We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.
(7) Your rights
You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).
You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)
(8) Third party websites
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.
(9) Updating information
Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.
(10) Contact
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us at Status Instruments Ltd, Status Business Park, Gannaway Lane, Tewkesbury, Gloucestershire. GL20 8FD
Can't find what you're looking for?
COMPANY Status Instruments Ltd,
Status Business Park,
Gannaway Lane,
Tewkesbury,
Glos,
GL20 8FD.
© 2020 Copyright 2019. Status Instruments Ltd.
Website Terms of use | Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions | Sitemap
Top
How can we help?
Tell us what you are looking to achieve & we will aim to provide the best solution and price. Rather speak to someone?
Call 01684 296818.
HOW DID YOU HEAR ABOUT US? ---Search EngineSocial mediaReferralAdvertisement
By using this form you agree with the storage and handling of your data by this website.
We’ll do our best to respond within 4 working hours.
If you need a quicker response, please call us on
01684 296818.
